<!-- res/values/calculators.xml -->
<resources>
    <string-array name="calculator_names">
        <item>One Rep Max Calculator</item>
        <item>Drop-set Calculator</item>
        <item>Super-set Calculator</item>
        <item>Reverse Pyramid Calculator</item>
        <item>Pyramid Calculator</item>
        <item>Rest-pause Calculator</item>
        <item>Tabata</item>
        <!-- Add more items as needed -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="calculator_descriptions">
        <item>One Rep Max (1RM) is a vital metric in weight training, representing the maximum amount of weight an individual can lift for a single repetition with proper form. It\'s crucial for designing effective strength training programs.\n\nCalculation Methods:\n\nEpley Formula: Estimates 1RM using weight lifted and repetitions performed.\n\nBrzycki Formula: Calculates 1RM based on weight lifted and repetitions.\n\nLombardi Formula: Provides an alternative approach to estimating 1RM using weight lifted and repetitions.</item>
        <item>Drop Set is a weightlifting technique where an individual performs a set of an exercise to failure or near failure, then reduces the weight and continues with another set without rest. This process can be repeated for multiple sets, decreasing the weight each time.</item>
        <item>Description of Super-set Calculator</item>
        <item>Reverse Pyramid Training is a weightlifting technique where an individual starts with a heavier weight and lower repetitions in the first set, then gradually decreases the weight and increases the repetitions with each subsequent set. This method allows for maximal effort in the initial sets when strength levels are highest, followed by metabolic fatigue and muscular endurance in the later sets. Each set is performed to near failure or complete failure, providing a challenging workout that targets both strength and hypertrophy. Reverse Pyramid Training can be an effective way to stimulate muscle growth and improve overall strength and endurance.</item>
        <item>Description of Pyramid Calculator</item>
        <item>Description of Rest-pause Calculator</item>
        <item>Description of Tabata</item>
        <!-- Add descriptions for other calculators as needed -->
    </string-array>
</resources>
